{"problem":[
    {"pid":1, "question": "How old is Philip Nguyen?",
        "choices": ["23 years old", "22 years old", "24 years old", "21 years old"], "answer": "22 years old"},
    {"pid":2, "question": "What was Philip's first programming language?",
        "choices": ["Python", "Java", "C", "SQL"], "answer": "Python"},
    {"pid":3, "question": "What is Philip's favorite food?",
        "choices": ["Pizza", "Eggs", "Steak", "Fried rice"], "answer": "Eggs"},
    {"pid":4, "question": "What college/university did Philip attend?",
        "choices": ["Harvard", "UC Davis", "Arizona State University", "UC Irvine"], "answer": "UC Irvine"},
    {"pid":5, "question": "Who is Philip's favorite superhero?",
        "choices": ["Batman", "Akash", "Spider-Man", "Bhawna Gunwani"], "answer": "Spider-Man"},
    {"pid":6, "question": "Where is Philip from?",
        "choices": ["NYC", "San Jose", "Austin", "LA"], "answer": "San Jose"},
    {"pid":7, "question": "What was Philip's previous job before joining TCS?",
        "choices": ["Chick-fil-A cashier", "Martial arts teacher", "Babysitter", "TCS is his first ever job!"], "answer": "TCS is his first ever job!"},
    {"pid":8, "question": "What computer device does Philip own, besides the TCS laptop?",
        "choices": ["Dell laptop", "MacBook Air", "MacBook Pro", "None of the above"], "answer": "MacBook Air"},
    {"pid":9, "question": "Which of these statements is true about Philip?",
        "choices": ["Philip knows how to backflip", "Philip lives with his parents", "Philip hates pineapple on pizza", "Philip is a software engineering major"], "answer": "Philip knows how to backflip"},  
    {"pid":10, "question": "Which answer is correct?",
        "choices": ["True", "False", "Yes", "No"], "answer": "False"}
]}